Gort: So what are we waiting for?
Reniesta: I feel the information pass through me, but I cannot understand anything... What's going on, Klavdia?!
Klavdia: Everything is as it should be. This form of knowledge is not designed to be perceived by weak minds. But I understand everything perfectly.
Klavdia: This is what we were looking for. The world that Nihaz was trying to hide. The world he wants to conquer. The world...
Nihaz: ...of your mother. I shouldn't have expected you to be sentimental... There are other secrets in this Citadel...
Klavdia: I know what I'm looking for. I don't need your advice.
Nihaz: I don't doubt it. You are very fortunate that I'm busy with this invasion.
Nihaz: Wait a second... That's not you.
Nihaz: She let you into her memories...?
Nihaz: How... curious.